He Shi,
how dare you throw me under the bus
and enjoy yourself here?
Are you even human?
Isn't this all for us?
Think about it.
If we both go down,
how are we going to survive this storm?
So you chose to sacrifice me
and said I seduced you?
It was clearly you back then...
What's wrong?
You look upset.
It's not like your dad has been ignoring
me for just a day or two.
Ever since his health declined,
he hasn't touched me.
Dad is really blind.
I am Mrs. He now.
I was young and ignorant back then.
You were already an adult.
And
you actually gave me a fake watch,
which almost made me
end up on the streets.
How could it be a fake watch?
Shu Roujing must have swapped it.
You know she married me
just for the money.
You're not lying to me again, are you?
I would never lie to you.
He Shi,
I'm done for.
If I go back to the He family,
the master will definitely kill me.
You're all I have left.
If you dare to betray me
or abandon me again,
I'll expose the fact
that you killed the butler.
You're so beautiful.
How could I?
I even prepared a gift for you.
It's so expensive.
Do you like it?
This is more suitable
for a young girl, isn't it?
In my eyes,
you'll always be eighteen.
He Shi,
Didn't you ask me
why I'm so skilled at disposing of bodies?
Because it wasn't
my first time killing someone.
Do you know
why the orphanage was abandoned?
Because I buried the director
here too.
It's all of you.
You ruined me.
Why did you push me?
Why did you have to push me?
You all forced me.
What did I do wrong?
It's all your fault...
Don't worry.
It's just a minor surgery.
It's not life-threatening.
Don't be afraid.
I'll be waiting right here for you.
Thank you, He Yu.
I want to hear
you call my name just once.
He Yu.
Family members, please wait outside.
Dad,
we'll all be fine.
I don't need you in the room today.
Don't come in
without my permission.
You may leave.
Yes.
Honey,
what happened to you?
Young Master,
today is the day
of Zhangxin's transplant surgery for Dad.
I know you don't really care about this,
but
I still need to tell you.
I've been thinking lately.
I don't want us to end up like this.
You know,
we used to be so good together,
and now
we're like enemies.
Don't you think it's a shame?
Didn't you say
I was boring in bed
and couldn't satisfy your special kinks?
So,
I went
and learned a few tricks.
Be good.
Wait for me.
Honey.
Don't you like excitement?
What are you doing?
I'm your husband.
Honey,
it's been so long since you touched me.
Shu Roujing,
are you crazy?
Honey.
Honey,
I was wrong.
I'll go disinfect
and be right back.
Honey,
where are you going?
you're really pitiful.
You have a very serious disease.
Whenever you meet a woman,
you go into heat anytime, anywhere.
If you're not satisfied,
you suffer.
Let me help you cut out
the root of the problem,
okay?